question_data = [
    {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In the 1988 film 'Akira', Tetsuo ends up destroying Tokyo.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The animated film 'Spirited Away' won the Academy Award for Best Animated Feature at the 75th Academy Awards in 2003.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Studio Ghibli is a Japanese animation studio responsible for the films 'Wolf Children' and 'The Boy and the Beast'.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The anime 'Lucky Star' follows the story of one girl who is unaware she is God.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The anime Attack on Titan was directed by Tetsur\u014d Araki, the same person who directed the anime Highschool of the Dead.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "Throughout the entirety of 'Dragon Ball Z', Goku only kills two characters: a miniboss named Yakon and Kid Buu.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The name of the attack 'Kamehameha' in Dragon Ball Z was named after a famous king of Hawaii.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "Druid is a mage class in 'Log Horizon'.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "The character Plum from 'No Game No Life' is a girl.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "The protagonist in 'Humanity Has Declined' has no discernable name and is simply referred to as &#039;I&#039; for most of the series.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}
]
